Terms of Use for Browser Extensions
-----------------------------------

These terms govern the use of Browser Extensions by The Provider - hereinafter also being referred to as “the Service” – which is implemented, operated and hosted by the company LinkResearchTools GmbH (“the Provider” or “LRT”).

By installing registration to the Service you hereinafter referred to as “the Client” agree to be bound by the following [Terms and Conditions](https://www.linkresearchtools.com/legal/terms.md#terms-and-conditions "Version: September 29, 2020 These terms govern the use of the website and services of LinkResearchTools (LRT) and Link Detox - hereinafter also being referred to as "the Service" – which is implemented, operated and hosted by the company LinkResearchTools GmbH ("the Provider" or “LRT”).") (this “Agreement”) below. If the Client objects to anything in this Agreement, the Client cannot use the Service.

By downloading, installing and/or using our Browser Extensions, you hereinafter referred to as “the Client” agree to be bound by the following [Terms and Conditions](https://www.linkresearchtools.com/legal/terms.md#terms-and-conditions "Version: September 29, 2020 These terms govern the use of the website and services of LinkResearchTools (LRT) and Link Detox - hereinafter also being referred to as "the Service" – which is implemented, operated and hosted by the company LinkResearchTools GmbH ("the Provider" or “LRT”).") (this “Agreement”) below. If the Client objects to anything in this Agreement, the Client cannot use the Service.

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted clearly on our website. You are encouraged to review the [privacy policy](https://www.linkresearchtools.com/legal/privacy.md#privacy-policy) whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any information you provide will be used.

Downloading the Browser Extension
---------------------------------

We do not collect nor store any personally identifiable information about you, except if you choose to opt-in to a data saving feature. In this case, we will collect and store your data in a European data center. You will be asked for your explicit consent before any data is collected or stored.

It is important that you are aware of the following ways we process some data coming from the computer where the Browser Extension is installed.

For every web page you view while using the Browser Extension, we need access to your IP address, the full general information about your browser, the URL you visit and general information about your computer’s operating system. We use this information to enable the functionality of the Browser Extension.

We may collect anonymous automated statistics of the use of the Browser Extension. These statistics include such data as the URLs visited, the frequency of use of the options, and other user activities within the Browser Extension. We use the third party service Google Analytics to collect the statistics. We do not control how they handle the data being processed, so please familiarize yourself with Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkresearchtools.com/legal/privacy.md#privacy-policy) at [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) before you start using the Toolbar.

These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, date of the visit, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information. Google has additional information available about their Google Analytics Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.

The Provider does not attempt to analyze web usage data to determine the identity of any Browser Extension user. The Provider aggregates and analyzes the information it collects to improve its service and to prepare reports about aggregate web usage.

Our servers where this data is sent to are located in Europe. We do keep aggregate information about the sent data for an unspecified time in various aggregates.

Data Sharing
------------

The Provider does not share any information about the specific detail data with third parties or the public, unless required by law. If you wish to disable collection of the data for the Browser Extension, then you need to uninstall the extension. The Browser Extension is automatically disabled when browsing in private mode.

Users may have the option to share parts of their data (e.g. Prompts, Comments) with the public, in which case it will be visible to anyone and can be used by anyone. You agree that sharing such data you enter and share to the public may contain personally identifiable or other sensitive information at your own risk.

Data Security
-------------

The Provider takes the security of your data seriously and has implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage.

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal data you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities.

However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Information about visited URLs handled through the Browser Extension
--------------------------------------------------------------------

The Browser Extension will have access to all web pages you open through the browser where the Browser Extension is installed. Furthermore, any data you enter into the address bar, along with your IP address, is transmitted to The Provider. You agree that such data you enter into the address bar may contain personally identifiable or other sensitive information at your own risk.

No Resale or Redistribution of Service
--------------------------------------

Except as expressly authorized by The Provider, you agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, trade, resell, modify, create derivative works, or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Browser Extension, or access to the Service or computer code that powers the Service.

Blocking of IP Addresses
------------------------

To protect the integrity of the Browser Extension, The Provider reserves the right at any time in its sole discretion to block Registrants and Members from certain IP addresses from accessing the Website.

Using our Browser Extensions
----------------------------

Using our Browser Extensions does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the content you access.
